New York State Labor Documentation Project on Microfilm 5787 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Carpenters Local 532, Elmira, NY - Dupe, 1909-1919 (Reel 5457)
- Carpenters Local 532, Elmira, NY - Dupe, 1920-1927 (Reel 5458)
- Carpenters Local 532, Elmira, NY - Dupe, 1927-1943 (Reel 5459)
- Carpenters Local 532, Elmira, NY - Dupe, 1943-1949 (Reel 5460)
- Carpenters Local 532, Elmira, NY - Dupe, 1949-1967 (Reel 5461)
- District 65, U.A.W. Minutes (Reel 5500)
  Positive
- District 65, U.A.W. Minutes (Reel 5501)
- District 65, U.A.W. Minutes (Reel 5502)
- District 65, U.A.W. Minutes (Reel 5503)
- District 65, U.A.W. Minutes (Reel 5504)
- District 65, U.A.W. Minutes (Reel 5505)
- District 65, U.A.W. Minutes (Reel 5506)
- District 65, U.A.W. Minutes (Reel 5507)
- District 65, U.A.W. Minutes (Reel 5508)
- District 65, U.A.W. Minutes (Reel 5509)
- District 65, U.A.W. Minutes (Reel 5510)
- District 65, U.A.W. Minutes (Reel 5511)
- District 65, U.A.W. Minutes (Reel 5512)
- District 65, U.A.W. Minutes (Reel 5513)
- District 65, U.A.W. Minutes (Reel 5514)
- District 65, U.A.W. Minutes (Reel 5515)
- District 65, U.A.W. Minutes (Reel 5516)
- District 65, U.A.W. Minutes (Reel 5517)
- District 65, U.A.W. Minutes (Reel 5518)
- The Civil Service Leader, 1946-1947 (Reel 9349)
- The Civil Service Leader, 1950-1951 (Reel 9350)
- The Civil Service Leader, 1952-1953 (Reel 9351)
- The Civil Service Leader, 1954-1955 (Reel 9352)
- The Civil Service Leader, 1956-1957 (Reel 9353)
- The Civil Service Leader, 1958-1959 (Reel 9354)
- The Civil Service Leader, 1960-1961 (Reel 9355)
- The Civil Service Leader, 1962-1963 (Reel 9356)
- The Civil Service Leader, 1966-1967 (Reel 9357)
- The Civil Service Leader, 1964-1965 (Reel 9358)
- The Civil Service Leader, 1970-1971 (Reel 9359)
- The Civil Service Leader, 1972-1973 (Reel 9360)
- The Civil Service Leader, 1974-1975 (Reel 9361)
- The Civil Service Leader, 1976-1977 (Reel 9362)
- Constitutions and Bylaws, 1954-1968; 1 (Reel 9363)
  1954, 1968
- Minutes, 1951-1989; 2 (Reel 9363)
- Bulletin, 1919-1938; 1 (Reel 9364)
  1919-20, 1930, 1935-36, 1938
- Newspaper Clippings, 1929-1937; 2 (Reel 9364)
  1929-33, 1937
- Official Calls for Conferences, 1983-1990; 3 (Reel 9364)
  1983, 1985-88, 1990
- Proceedings, 1934-1975; 4 (Reel 9364)
  1934, 1938-75
- Program for Conference, 1979; 5 (Reel 9364)
- Officers and Executive Board Meeting Minutes, 1969-1979; 1 (Reel 9365)
  1969-70, 1975-79
- Officers and Executive Board Meeting Minutes, 1980-1985; 2 (Reel 9366)
- Membership Meeting Minutes, 1975-1985; 3 (Reel 9367)
- The Civil Service Leader, 1978-1980; 1 (Reel 9368)
- The Civil Service Leader, 1981-1983; 1 (Reel 9369)
- The Civil Service Leader, 1984-1986; 1 (Reel 9370)
- The Civil Service Leader, 1987-1989; 1 (Reel 9371)
- UE Local 301 News, Schenectady, New York, 1947-1954; 4 (Reel 9372)
  April 1947-June 1954
- IUE Local 301 News, 1954-1990; 5 (Reel 9373)
  April 2, 1954-July 1990
- Series Subject Files, 1941-2001
  - The Local 301 Story, 1968; 1 (Reel 9374)
  - National Labor Relations Board Election Between IUE and UE, 1951; 2 (Reel 9374)
  - Power Efficiency Program, 1985; 3 (Reel 9374)
  - Press Releases, 1967-1971; 4 (Reel 9374)
  - Press Releases, 1972-1978; 5 (Reel 9374)
  - Retirees Club Meeting Minutes, 1972-1983; 6 (Reel 9374)
  - Schenectady Area Industrial Unions Council--Photograph, 1955; 7 (Reel 9374)
    ca. 1955
  - Schenectady Industrial Development Council (formerly GUTS), 1960-1961; 8 (Reel 9374)
  - Shambo, John, 1970; 9 (Reel 9374)
    ca. 1970
  - The Story of Local 301, IUE-AFL-CIO, 1987; 10 (Reel 9374)
  - Teachers' Strike, 1975; 11 (Reel 9374)
    ca. 1975
  - Testimony Before the McCarthy Senate Committee on Unemployment, 1960; 12 (Reel 9374)
  - Strikes, Photographs, 1966-1969; 13 (Reel 9374)
    1966, 1969
  - UE Factsheets, 1960; 14 (Reel 9374)
  - Anniversary Book for Local 301's Fiftieth Anniversary, 1986; 1 (Reel 9375)
  - Bulletins and Notices, 1981-1982; 2 (Reel 9375)
  - Bulletins and Notices, 1979-1980; 3 (Reel 9375)
  - Constitution and By-Laws, 1959-1978; 4 (Reel 9375)
    1959, 1978
  - Constitutions and By-Laws of IUE and IUE District Council 3, 1949-1979; 5 (Reel 9375)
    1949, 1954, 1959, 1965, 1979
  - Constitution Committee, 1958-1959; 6 (Reel 9375)
  - Contract Benefit Manuals, 1970-1973; 7 (Reel 9375)
    1970, 1973
  - Contract Negotiations, 1969-1973; 8 (Reel 9375)
  - Coordinated Bargaining Committee--General Electric and Westinghouse Unions, 1969; 9 (Reel 9375)
  - Coordinated Bargaining Committee--General Electric and Westinghouse Unions, 1973; 10 (Reel 9375)
  - Correspondence, 1974-1975; 11 (Reel 9375)
  - Correspondence to Editor of Schenectady Gazette, 1969-1974; 12 (Reel 9375)
    1969, 1974
  - Dual Unionism, 1971; 13 (Reel 9375)
    ca. 1971
  - Education Committee--Photograph, 1979; 14 (Reel 9375)
  - Employee Benefits Manual, 1966; 15 (Reel 9375)
  - Record of Resolution or Motion, 1961-1963; 1 (Reel 9376)
  - Record of Resolution or Motion, 1964-1966; 1 (Reel 9377)
  - Record of Resolution or Motion, 1966-1967; 1 (Reel 9378)
  - Record of Resolution or Motion, 1968-1969; 1 (Reel 9379)
- Series Legal Files, 1974-1979, 1981-1983:
  - Agreements Between CSEA and New York State, 1977-1979; 1 (Reel 9380)
  - Legal Committee Meeting Minutes, 1982-1983; 2 (Reel 9380)
  - Legal Committee Reports, 1981-1983; 3 (Reel 9380)
  - Model Chapter Constitution, 1974-1975; 4 (Reel 9380)
  - Model Regional Constitution, 1974-1975; 5 (Reel 9380)
  - Model Unit Constitution, 1975; 6 (Reel 9380)
  - Regional Attorney Meeting, 1976; 7 (Reel 9380)
- Series Series 1: Minutes, 1947-88
  - Sub-Series General Membership Meeting Minutes, 1947-74, 1979-88
    - Amalgamated Lithographers of America, Local 59, 1947-1964; 1 (Reel 9381)
    - Lithographers and Photoengravers International Union, Local 59-L/259, 1964-1966; 2 (Reel 9381)
    - Lithographers and Photoengravers International Union, Local 259-M, 1967-1972; 3 (Reel 9381)
    - Graphic Arts International Union, Local 259-M, 1973-1974; 4 (Reel 9381)
    - Graphic Arts International Union, Local 259-M, 1979-1982; 5 (Reel 9381)
    - Graphic Communications International Union, Local 259-M, 1983-1988; 6 (Reel 9381)
  - Sub-Series Executive Board Meeting Minutes, 1950-56, 1960-88
    - Amalgamated Lithographers of America, Local 59, 1950-1956; 1 (Reel 9381)
      Minutes of Council Board Meetings
    - Amalgamated Lithographers of America, Local 59, 1960-1964; 2 (Reel 9381)
    - Lithographers and Photoengravers International Union, Local 259-M, 1965-1972; 3 (Reel 9381)
    - Graphic Arts International Union, Local 259-M, 1973-1981; 4 (Reel 9381)
    - Graphic Communications International Union, Local 259-M, 1982-1988; 5 (Reel 9381)
      Minutes of Executive Board Meetings
- Series Series 2: Subject Files, 1946-49, 1951-52, 1955, 1959, 1961-88.
  - Agendas for Council Board Meetings, 1973-1979; 1 (Reel 9382)
  - Agendas for Executive Board Meetings, 1980-1985; 2 (Reel 9382)
  - Agendas for General Membership Meetings, 1973-1985; 3 (Reel 9382)
  - Alfred Publishing--Organizing, 1985; 4 (Reel 9382)
  - Amsterdam Printing and Litho Corporation, 1980; 5 (Reel 9382)
  - Amsterdam Printing and Litho Corporation--Litigation over Refusal to Recognize Union, 1973-1975; 6 (Reel 9382)
  - Amsterdam Printing and Litho Corporation--Litigation over Refusal to Recognize Union, 1975-1980; 1 (Reel 9383)
  - Argus Press--Contract, 1987; 2 (Reel 9383)
  - Baronet Litho, Inc.--Contract, 1986; 3 (Reel 9383)
  - By-Laws, 1951-1983; 4 (Reel 9383)
    1951, 1963, ca. 1964, ca. 1972, ca. 1983
  - Capital Newspapers Division, The Hearst Corporation--Contracts with LPIU Local 21-P, 1964-1965; 5 (Reel 9383)
  - The Color Shop--Contract, 1976; 6 (Reel 9383)
  - Committee to Elect Emery B. Miller for President, 1987; 7 (Reel 9383)
    ca. 1987
  - Correspondence of ALA Local 59, 1948-1949; 8 (Reel 9383)
  - Correspondence of ALA Local 59, 1951-1952; 9 (Reel 9383)
  - Crest Litho Inc.--Contract, 1988; 10 (Reel 9383)
  - Dinner Journals, 1962-1987; 11 (Reel 9383)
    1962-70, 1972-75, 1977, 1983, 1985, 1987
  - Dodge-Graphic Press, Inc.--Contract, 1988; 12 (Reel 9383)
  - Greenwood Company--Contract with ALA Local 59, 1955; 13 (Reel 9383)
  - List of Shops with GCIU Local 259-M Contracts, 1988; 14 (Reel 9383)
    ca. 1988
  - The Maqua Company--Contract with ALA Local 59, 1951; 15 (Reel 9383)
  - The Maqua Company--Contract Meetings with ALA Local 59, 1959; 16 (Reel 9383)
  - The Maqua Company--Strike and Strikebreaking, 1970-1977; 17 (Reel 9383)
  - Merger of GCIU Locals 259-M and 58-C, 1987; 18 (Reel 9383)
  - Metro Data Repro Graphics--Contract, 1988; 19 (Reel 9383)
  - Saratoga Printing Company--Representation Election, 1973-1974; 20 (Reel 9383)
  - Troy Record Company--Contracts with IPEU and LPIU No. 21, 1946-1965; 21 (Reel 9383)
    1946-48,1951-52, 1961-65
- Series Series 3: Utica Graphic Communications Local No. 58-C, GCIU Subject Files, 1941, 1946, 1950-53, 1957, 1959-86
  - Constitution, 1977; 1 (Reel 9384)
  - Crowley Publishing Corporation, 1957-1965; 2 (Reel 9384)
    1957, 1959-60, 1962, 1965
  - Daily Star--Contracts, 1975-1986; 3 (Reel 9384)
    1975, 1980, 1982, 1986
  - Dodge-Graphic Press, Inc.--Contracts, 1976-1985; 4 (Reel 9384)
    1976, 1979-80, 1982, 1985
  - Evans, David--Hearings Before Union, 1963-1969; 5 (Reel 9384)
    1963, 1966-69
  - Hughes, Leland--Hearing Before Union, 1963-1968; 6 (Reel 9384)
    1963, 1967-68
  - Jones Stephenson Company--Arbitration, 1952-1953; 7 (Reel 9384)
  - Merger Considerations of the International Printing Pressmen & Assistants' Union of North America, 1972; 8 (Reel 9384)
  - Metzler Printing--Contracts, 1979-1982; 9 (Reel 9384)
    1979, 1982
  - Notices to Local's Members, 1983; 10 (Reel 9384)
  - Oneonta Star--Contracts, 1965-1984; 11 (Reel 9384)
    1965, 1968-73, 1975, 1977, 1980, 1983-84
  - Rome Sentinel Company--Contracts, 1961-1982; 12 (Reel 9384)
    1961, 1972-82
  - Scononda Press, Inc.--Contracts, 1968-1982; 13 (Reel 9384)
    1968, 1970, 1972, 1975-76, 1979, 1981-82
  - Thomas C. Peters Printing Co., Inc., 1959-1984; 14 (Reel 9384)
    1959, 1972-73, 1976-77, 1980-81, 1984
  - Thomas C. Peters Printing Co., Inc.--Contracts, 1967-1985; 15 (Reel 9384)
    1967, 1979-82, 1985
  - Utica Observer-Dispatch--Arbitration over Contracts, 1941-1946; 16 (Reel 9384)
    1941, 1946
  - Utica Observer-Dispatch--Arbitration over Contracts, 1950-1951; 1 (Reel 9385)
  - Utica Observer-Dispatch--Arbitration over Demand for Arbitration, 1965; 2 (Reel 9385)
  - Utica Observer-Dispatch--Arbitration over Holidays, 1967-1968; 3 (Reel 9385)
  - Utica Observer-Dispatch--Arbitration over Manning of New Presses, 1971; 4 (Reel 9385)
  - Utica Observer-Dispatch--Arbitration over Overtime, 1962-1968; 5 (Reel 9385)
  - Utica Observer-Dispatch--Arbitration over Overtime and Improper Relief from Duty, 1963-1967; 6 (Reel 9385)
    1963, 1965-67
  - Utica Observer-Dispatch--Contracts, 1950-1984; 7 (Reel 9385)
    1950, 1967-81, 1984
  - Utica Observer-Dispatch--Correspondence, 1960-1984; 8 (Reel 9385)
    1960-62, 1966, 1969, 1984
  - Utica Observer-Dispatch--Strike, 1966-1967; 9 (Reel 9385)
- Series City Teacher's Association of Schenectady, 1918-34, 1937-43
  - General Files, 1937-1943; 1 (Reel 9386)
  - General Files, 1940-1943; 2 (Reel 9386)
  - Minutes of City Teacher's Association of Schenectady, 1918-1924; 3 (Reel 9386)
  - Minutes of City Teacher's Association of Schenectady, 1924-1934; 4 (Reel 9386)
  - Minutes of Delegate Assembly of the Department of Public Instruction of Schenectady, 1928-1931; 5 (Reel 9386)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1933; 6 (Reel 9386)
- Series Schenectady Federation of Teachers, AFT Local 803, 1942-89
  - Charter, 1944; 7 (Reel 9386)
- Series Series 1: Minutes, 1944-89
  - Minutes of Regular Meetings, Executive Committee Meetings, and Building Directors' Meetings, 1944-1955; 8 (Reel 9386)
  - Minutes of Regular Meetings, Executive Committee Meetings, and Building Directors' Meetings, 1955-1979; 1 (Reel 9387)
  - Minutes of Executive Committee Meetings, 1979-1989; 1 (Reel 9388)
  - Minutes of Building Directors' Meetings, 1973-1989; 2 (Reel 9388)
    1973-76, 1978-80, 1983-89
- Series Series 2: Subject Files, 1944-80, 1982-85, 1987
  - Building Director's Handbook, 1975; 1 (Reel 9389)
  - Bulletins to Teachers, 1953-1984; 2 (Reel 9389)
    1953-65, 1971-72, 1977, 1979, 1984
  - Calendars and Agendas, 1956-1969; 3 (Reel 9389)
  - Constitutions, 1944-1980; 4 (Reel 9389)
    ca. 1944, 1955, 1967, 1972-73, 1975-76, 1980
  - Contracts, 1967-1987; 5 (Reel 9389)
    1967, 1971, 1973, 1975, 1977-78, 1980, 1982-84, 1987
  - Convention and Conference Reports, 1974; 6 (Reel 9389)
  - Crisis Committee, 1984-1985; 7 (Reel 9389)
  - Curriculum Committees, 1971-1972; 8 (Reel 9389)
  - Educational Policies Advisory Committee, 1970-1973; 9 (Reel 9389)
  - Forum and Dinner Meeting Programs, 1946-1960; 10 (Reel 9389)
    1946-48, 1954, 1956-60
  - General Files, 1944-1947; 11 (Reel 9389)
  - General Files, 1948-1953; 1 (Reel 9390)
  - Graduate Steering Committee, 1972; 2 (Reel 9390)
  - Liaison Committee, 1956-1975; 1 (Reel 9391)
    1956-61, 1971-1975
  - Membership Lists, 1955-1969; 2 (Reel 9391)
  - Merit Rating, 1948-1964; 3 (Reel 9391)
    1948-49, 1952, 1964
  - Photographs, 1978-1979; 4 (Reel 9391)
  - President's Files, 1942-1955; 5 (Reel 9391)
  - Salary and Benefits Committee, 1964-1965; 6 (Reel 9391)
  - Salary Negotiations, 1984; 7 (Reel 9391)
  - Salary Study Committee, 1973-1974; 8 (Reel 9391)
  - Schenectady Teachers Association Decertification, 1972; 9 (Reel 9391)
  - Strike, 1975; 10 (Reel 9391)
  - Strike--Flyers and Notices, 1975; 11 (Reel 9391)
  - Strike--Photographs, 1975-1976; 12 (Reel 9391)
  - Strike--Picket Bulletin, 1975; 13 (Reel 9391)
  - Teacher Representation, 1967-1970; 14 (Reel 9391)
  - Federation News, 1956-1963; 1 (Reel 9392)
    1956-60, 1962-63
  - Soft News, 1964-1971; 2 (Reel 9392)
  - SFT Newsletter, 1972-1974; 3 (Reel 9392)
  - SFT Pipeline, 1974-1989; 4 (Reel 9392)